Professor Richard Jonas Papers, 1990-1992
University of Houston Libraries
- University Related
  - Faculty and Staff Activities and Groups
    - American Association of University Professors: President, 1944-1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - American Association of University Professors: Salary Ranking, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - American Association of University Professors: South West Conference-Lake Texoma, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - American Association of University Professors: Tax, 1957-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - American Association of University Professors: Texas Conference, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - American Association of University Professors: UH Chapter, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - American Association of University Professors: UH Chapter, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - American Association of University Professors: UH Chapter, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Assembly, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Assembly, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Assembly, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Assembly: Committee on Improvement of Teaching, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Faculty Assembly: Constitution, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Assembly: Emeritus Scroll Committee, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Assembly: Faculty Welfare Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Assembly: L.S. Mitchell Committee, 1942-1954 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Faculty Assembly: Meetings, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Faculty Assembly: Planning Committee, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Faculty Assembly: Planning Committee, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Assembly: Planning Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Assembly: Student Welfare Committee, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Association, 1944-1946 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Association, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Faculty Association, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Faculty Association, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Association, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Association, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Association, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Faculty Association, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Association, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Faculty Association, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Faculty Association, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Faculty Association, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Faculty Association, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Faculty Association, 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Faculty Club, 1950-1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Committees, 1938-1949 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Council, 1952-1958 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Development Leave, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1944-1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Faculty News Letter", 1947-1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Receptions, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Orientation, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Recreation, 1963-1971 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1945-1950 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Senate, 1963-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Senate: Constitution, 1960-1962 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Senate: Minutes, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Senate: Minutes, January 18, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Senate: Newsletter, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Senate: Students Affairs Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Faculty and Staff Listings, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Teaching Awards, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Faculty Tenure and Promotion, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Vacation Policy, 1947-1949 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Financial Policy, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Professors Association of UH, 1946-1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - South Central Renaissance Conference, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Spencer, Dr. Terrel (Newspaper Article), 1955 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Sunday Evening Club, 1952-1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Sunday Evening Club, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Sunday Evening Club, 1972-1979 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Sunday Evening Club-PhD Lang Exams, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Town and Gown, 1960-1972 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Twenty Year Club, 1958-1980 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - University Governance Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 31)